when you train your neural network, it is
当你训练神经网络,
important to initialize the weights
权重随机初始化是很重要的
randomly for logistic regression it was
对于逻辑回归，当然
okay to initialize the weights to zero
把权重初始化为0也是可以的,
but for a neural network if you initialize
但是对于一个神经网络
the weights the parameters to all zero in
如果你把权重或者参数都初始化为0
an apply of gradient descent, it won't work.
那么梯度下降将不会起作用。
let's see why, so you have here two input
让我们看看这是为什么，有两个输入
features so n0 is equal to two and two
特征，n0等于2，
hidden units so n1 is equal to two and
2个隐含层单元，n1就等于2
so the matrix associated with a hidden
因此与一个隐含层相关的矩阵
layer or w1 it is going to be 2x2 let's
或者说W1是2*2的矩阵，
say that you initialize it to all zeros
假设把它初始化为0，
0 0 0 0 2 by 2 matrix and let's say b1
0 0 0 0 2*2的矩阵，b1也
is also equal to 0 0 turns out
等于0 0，
initializing the bias terms B to 0 is
把偏置项b初始化为0是
actually okay but the initializing W to
合理的，但是把W初始化
all zeros is a problem so the problem
为0就有问题了，因此这个问题
with this formal initialization is that
如果按照这样初始化的话
for any example you give it you have
你总是会发现
that a 1 1 and a 1 2 will be equal all
a[1]1 和 a[1]2相等
right so this activation and this
这个激活单元和这个
activation would be same because both of
激活单元就会一样，因为两个
these hidden units are computing exactly
隐含单元计算
the same function and then when you
同样的函数，当你
compute back propagation it turns out
做反向传播计算时，这会导致
that dz1[1] and dz1[2] will also be the
dz[1]1 和 dz[1]2也会
same kind of by symmetry right both of
一样，对称
these hidden units will initialize the
这些隐含单元会初始化得
same way technically for what I'm saying
一样，这样
I'm assuming that the outgoing weights
输出的权值
are also identical so that W[2] is equal
也会一模一样，因此W[2] 等于
to 0 0 but if you initialize the neural
0 0，但是如果你这样初始化这个
network this way then this hidden unit
神经网络，那么这两个隐含单元
and this hidden unit are completely
就会完全一样
identical so they're completely
因此他们完全
sometimes you say they're completely
也就是完全对称
symmetric which just means that the
也就意味着
computing exactly the same function and
计算同样的函数
by kind of a proof by induction it turns
并且肯定的是最终
out that after every single iteration of
经过每次训练的迭代
training your two hidden units are
这两个隐含单元
still confusing exactly the same function
仍然是同一个函数，令人困惑。
since part of the show that DW will be a
dw会是
matrix that looks like this where every
一个这样的矩阵，每一行
row takes on the same value so we
有同样的值
perform a weight update so you perform
因此我们做权重更新
when you perform a weight update w[1] gets
把权重w[1]更新为
updated as w[1] minus alpha times DW you
w[1]减去alpha乘上dw
find that w1 after every iteration will
每次迭代后w[1]
have you know the first row equal to the
第一行等于
second row so it's possible to construct
第二行，可以推导
a proof by induction that if you
如果你
initialize all the ways all the values
把权重都初始化为
of W to 0 then because both hidden units
0，那么由于隐含单元
start off computing the same function
开始计算同一个函数
and both hidden units have the same
所有的隐含单元对
influence on the output unit then after
输出单元有同样的影响
one iteration that same statement is
一次迭代后同样的表达式
still true the two hidden units are
结果仍然是相同的 即隐含单元仍是
still symmetric and therefore by
对称的
induction after two iterations three
通过推导，两次、三次、、无论多少次
iterations and so on no matter how long
迭代，不管你
you train in your network both hidden
训练网络多长时间，隐含
units are still computing exactly the
单元仍然计算的是同样的
same function and so in this case
函数。因此这种情况下
there's really no point to having more
超过1个隐含单元也
than one hidden unit because they're all
没什么意义，因为
computing the same thing and of course
他们计算同样的东西，当然
for larger neural networks let's say you have
更大的网络，比如你有
three features and maybe a very large
3个特征，还有相当多的
number of hidden units a similar
隐含单元，
argument works to show that what the new
差不多长这个样子
network like this because I won't drawn
我不会画出
all the edges if you initialize the way
所有的边了，如果你要初始化成0
to zero then all of your hidden units
那么所有的隐含单元
are symmetric and no matter how long you
都是对称的，无论你
run gradient descent they'll all
运行梯度下降多久，他们一直
continue to compute exactly the same function
计算同样的函数
so that's not helpful because
这没有任何帮助，因为
you want two different hidden units to
你想要两个不同的隐含单元
compute different functions the solution
计算不同的函数
to this is to initialize your parameters
这个问题的解决方法就是随机初始化参数，
randomly so here's what you do you can
你应该这么做：
set W 1 equals NP got random dot R and n
把W1设为np.random.randn
of this generates our Gaussian random
(生成高斯分布)
variable 2 2 and then usually you
（2,2），通常
multiply this by a very small number
再乘上一个小的数
such as 0.01 so you initialize it to
比如0.01，这样把它初始化为
very small random values and then be um
很小的随机数，然后b
it turns out that B does not have this
b没有这个
symmetry problem what's called a
对称的问题
symmetry breaking problem
（叫做symmetry breaking problem）
so it is okay to initialize B to just zeros
所以可以把b初始化为0
because so long as W is initialized
因为只要随机初始化w
randomly you start off with the
你就有不同的
different hidden units computing
隐含单元计算
different things and so you no longer
不同的东西，因此不会有
have this um symmetry breaking problem
symmetry breaking问题了。
and then similarly for w2 you can
相似的，对于W2你可以
initialize that randomly and b2 you can
随机初始化，b2可以
initialize that to zero so you might be
初始化为0，你也许
wondering you know where did this
会疑惑，这个
constant come from and why is it 0.01
常数从哪里来，为什么是0.01
why not put the number 100 or 1000, turns
而不是100或者1000。
out that we usually prefer to initialize
我们通常倾向于初始化为
the ways to very very small random values
很小的随机数
because um if you're using a
因为如果你用
tanh or sigmoid activation function
tanh或者sigmoid激活函数
or if you have a sigmoid even just at
或者说只在输出层有一个Sigmoid
the output layer if the waves are too large
如果（数值）波动太大
then when you compute the
当你计算
activation values remember that z1 is
激活值时
equal to w1 X plus B and then on a 1 is
Z1=w1X+B，
the activation function applied to z1 so
a1=Sigmoid（Z1）
if W is very big Z will be very big or
因此如果W很大，Z就会很大
these some values of Z will be either
Z的一些值（a）就会
very large or very small and so in that
很大或者很小，因此
case you're more likely to end up at
这种情况下你很可能停在
these flat parts of the tanh function or
tanh/sigmoid函数的平坦的地方
the sigmoid function where the slope of
这些地方
the gradient is very small
梯度很小
meaning that gradient descent would be
也就意味着梯度下降会
very slow and so learning would be very slow
很慢，因此学习也就很慢。
so just a recap if W is too large you're
回顾一下：如果W很大，那么你
more likely to end up even at the very
很可能最终停在（甚至在训练
start of training with very large values
刚刚开始的时候）Z很大的值
of Z which causes your tanh or sigmoid
这会造成tanh/Sigmoid
activation function to be saturated on
激活函数饱和在
the slowing down learning, if you don't
龟速的学习上，如果你没有
have any sigmoid or tanh activation
sigmoid/tanh激活
functions throughout your neural network
函数在你整个的神经网络里
this is less of an issue but if you're
就不成问题。但如果
doing binary classification and your
你做二分类并且
output unit is a sigmoid function then
你的输出单元是Sigmoid函数
you know you just don't want the initial
那么你不会想让初始
parameters to be too large so that's why
参数太大，因此这就是为什么
multiplying by 0.01 would be something
乘上0.01是
reasonable to try or any other small number
合理的尝试或者其他一些小数
and same for w2.
对于W2一样。
this can be np.random.randn I guess this
就是np.random.randn，我猜
would be 1 by 2 in this example times
会是1，2乘以
0.01 Sigma s there. So finally it turns
0.01(噢  这里少了个s)。事实上
out that sometimes they can be better
有时有比0.01更好的常数
constants than 0.01 when you're training
当你训练
a neural network with just one hidden
一个只有一层隐含层的网络时
layer this is a relatively shallow neural
（这是相对浅的神经
network without too many hidden layers
网络，没有太多的隐含层）
setting to 0.01 will probably work ok
设为0.01可能也可以
but when you're training a very very
但当你训练一个非常非常
deep neural network then you might want
深的神经网络，你可能
to pick a different constant rather than 0.01
会选择一个不同于的常数 而不是0.01
and in next week's material we will talk a
下一节课我们会
little bit about how and when you might
讨论怎么并且何时去
want to choose a different constant from 0.01
选择一个不同于0.01的常数
but either way it will usually end
但是无论如何它通常
up being a relatively small number
都会是个相对小的数
so that's it for this week's videos you now
好了 这就是这周的视频
know how to set up a neural network of a
你现在已经知道如何建立一个一层的神经网络了
hidden layer, initialize the parameters
初始化参数
make predictions using forward prop as
用前向传播预测
well as compute derivatives and it's in
还有计算导数，
gradient descent using back prop so that
结合反向传播用在梯度下降中
you should be able to do the quizzes as
因此你能够做测验了
well as this week's programing exercises best
还有疾病编程作业了
of luck with that I hope you have fun
祝你好运！希望你能在练习中找到乐趣
with my exercise and look forward to
并且期待
seeing you in the week 4 materials
在第四周看到你。